Guide to the Stanford University, Computer Science Department, HCI Group, CS547 Seminar Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videorecordings
  - Using Computers to Aid Communication, A Case Study, Neil Scott, Stanford Center for the Study of Language and Information, 1996-4-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ann Copestake, Greg Edwards, Elizabeth Macken, Neil Scott, Stanford Center for the Study of Language and Information, "Using Computers to Aid Communication, A Case Study" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1996-4-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - The Design and Long-term Use of a Personal Electronic Notebook, Thomas Erickson, Apple Computer, 1996-5-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Thomas Erickson, Apple Computer, "The Design and Long-Term Use of a Personal Electronic Notebook" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1996-5-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Heat & Dust: Designing Solutions on the Other Side of the World, Michael Graves, Apple Computer, 1996-5-17; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Michael Graves, Rao Machiraju, Apple Computer, "Heat & Dust: Designing Solutions on the Other Side of the World" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1996-5-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Play and Learning with Technology, Realities of the Marketplace, Ann McCormick, CAPS Mira Studio, 1996-5-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ann McCormick, CAPS Mira Studio, "Play and Learning with Technology, Realities of the Marketplace (paper available)" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1996-5-24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - The Interacting Design Awards, Lauralee Alben, Alben+Faris, Apple, Stanford, 1996-5-31; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Laualee Alben, Harry Sadler, Terry Winograd, Alben+Faris, Apple, Stanford, "The Interacting Design Awards" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1996-5-31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Marc Levoy, Stanford Computer Science, "The Digital Michelangelo Project" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1997-10-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - The WebTop - HotJava Views and Beyond, Don Gentner, JavaSoft, SUN Microsystems, 1997-10-17; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Don Gentner, JavaSoft, Sun Microsystem, "The WebTop - HotJava Views and Beyond" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1997-10-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Supporting Cooperative and Personal Surfing with a Desktop Assistant, Hannes Marais, DEC Systems Research Center, 1997-10-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Krishna Bharat, DEC Systems Research Center, "Supporting Cooperative and Personal Surfing with a Desktop Assistant" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1997-10-24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Finding Objects in Large Collections of Images, Jitendra Malik, UC Berkeley, 1997-10-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jitendra Malik, UC Berkeley, "Finding Objects in Large Collections of Images" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1997-10-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Intelligent Analysis/ Synthesis of Facial Imagery, Chris Bregler, Interval Research, and UC Berkeley, 1997-10-31; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Chris Bregler, Trevor Darrell, Interval Research and UC Berkeley, "Intelligent Analysis/Synthesis of Facial Imagery" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1997-10-31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - The First Noble Truth of Cyberspace: People are People Even in the MUD, Diane Schiano, Interval Research, 1997-1-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Diane Schiano, Interval Research, "The First Noble Truth of Cyberspace: People are People Even in the MUD" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1997-1-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Primitive Man in the Electronic Work Environment, Anatol Holt, University of Milano, 1997-11-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Anatol Holt, University of Milano, "Primitive Man in the Electronic Work Environment" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1997-11-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Less is More, More is Less, Bill Buxton, Alias Wavefront, 1997-11-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Bill Buxton, Alias Wavefront, "Less is More, More is Less" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1997-11-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Computer-Mediated Instructional Materials for Distribution over Networked Computers: From Theory to Practice, Bernard Gifford, UC Berkeley and Academic Systems, 1997-11-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Bernard Gifford, UC Berkeley and Academic Systems, "Computer-mediated instructional materials for distribution over networked computers: From theory to practice" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1997-11-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - HAL's Legacy: 2001's Computer as Dream and Reality, David Stork, Rioch California Research Center, 1997-1-17; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - David Stork, Rioch California Research Center (and visiting scholar in Psychology at Stanford), "HAL's Legacy: 2001's Computer as Dream and Reality" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1997-1-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Making Software Easier and More Fun with Social Interfaces, Karen Fries, Microsoft, 1997-1-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Karen Fries, Microsoft, "Making software easier and more fun with soical interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1997-1-24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Open Research Questions about Virtual Communities, Amy Bruckman, Georgia Tech, 1997-12-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Amy Bruckman, Georgia Tech, "Open Research Questions about Virtual Communities" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1997-12-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Test as You Build: An Approach To Creating New Interfaces, Ted Selker, IBM Almaden Research Center, 1997-1-31; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ted Selker, IBM Almaden Research Center, "Test as You Build: An Approach To Creating New Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1997-1-31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - A User Interface for Interacting with Heterogeneous Distributed Applications, Steve Cousins, Stanford Computer Science, 1997-2-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Steve B. Cousins, Stanford Computer Science PCD Project, "A User Interface for interacting with Heterogeneous Distributed Applications" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1997-2-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Information Design and Why It Matters, Robert Jacobson, SRI Consulting, 1997-2-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Robert Jacobson, SRI Consulting, "Information Design and Why It Matters" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1997-2-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Designing an Interface for Telesurgery, Jon Bowersox, Dept of Surgery, Stanford Medical School, 1997-2-28; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Bower Sox, MD, PhD, Department of Sugery, Stanford University School of Medicine, "Designing an Interface for Telesugery" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1997-2-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Risks and Their Prevention: The Role of the Human Interface, Peter G. Neumann, SRI International, 1997-2-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Peter G. Neumann, SRI INternational, "Risks and Their Prevention: The Role of the Human Interface" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1997-2-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Sensemaking II: What, Why and Whither People Use the WWW for Work, Dan Russell, Apple Research Labs, 1997-3-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Daniel Russell, Apple Research Labs, "Sensemaking II: What, why and whither people use the WWW for work" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1997-3-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Interface Design for Art, Peter Samis, SF MOMA, 1997-3-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Peter Samis, Steve Mayer, San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, with Steve Mayer, "Interface Design for Art" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1997-3-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - A Network-Centric Design for Relationship-based Rights Management, Martin Roscheisen, Stanford Computer Science (Digital Libraries Project), 1997-4-11; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Martin Roscheisen, Stanford Computer Science (Digital Libraries Project), "A Network-Centric Design for Relationship-based Rights Management" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1997-4-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Universal Access to the Net: Requirements and Social Impact, Jeff Johnson, UI Wizards, Inc, 1997-4-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jeff Johnson, UI Wizards, Inc, "Universal Access to the Net: Requirements and Social Impact" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1997-4-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Sensemaker: An Information-Exploration Interface, Michelle Wang Baldonado, Stanford Computer Science (Digital Libraries Project), 1997-4-25; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Michelle Wang Baldonado, Stanford Computer Science (Digital Libraries Project), "Sensemaker: An Information-Exploration Interface" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1997-4-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Speaking with your Voice, Pen, Eyes, Face, Hands, and Fingers, Alex Waibel, Interactive Systems Labs, CMU, 1997-4-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Alex Waibel, Interactive Systems Laboratories, Carnegie Mellon Univeristy and Univeristy of Karlsruhe, "Speaking with your Voice, Pen, Eyes, Face, Hands, and Fingers" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1997-4-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Negotiating Ontologies: Bridging the Gaps, Austin Henderson, Pliant Research, 1997-5-16; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Austin Henderson, Jed Harris, Pliant Research, "Negotiating Ontologies: bridging the gaps" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1997-5-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Tangible Bits: Towards Seamless Interface between People, Bits, and Atoms, Hiroshi Ishii, MIT Media Lab, 1997-5-2; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Hiroshi Ishii, MIT Media Lab, "Tangible Bits: Towards Seamless Interface between People, Bits, and Atoms" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1997-5-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Towards a New View of Information: History-Enriched Digital Objects and Dynamic Work Materials, Jim Hollan, Computer Science, UNM, 1997-5-23; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - James Hollan, Computer Science, UNM, "Towards A New View of Information: History-Enriched Digital Objects and Dynamic Work " (CS547 Winograd 8), 1997-5-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Towards the Third Generation of the PC: Lessons Learned from Thomas Edison, Don Norman, Hewlett-Packard Labs, 1997-5-30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Donald Norman, Hewlett-Packard Laboratories, "Towards the third generation of the PC: Lessons learned from Thomas Edison" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1997-5-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Technologies for Telecollaboration: Challenges and Opportunities in Image Capture, Rendering and Display, Henry Fuchs, University of North Carolina, 1997-5-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Henry Fuchs, University of North Carolina, "Technologies for Telecollaboration: Challenges and Opportunities in Image Capture, Rendering and Display" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1997-5-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Randy Pausch, Carnegie-Mellon University, "Disney's Aladdin: First Steps Towards Storytelling in Virtual Reality" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1997-9-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - The Life Cycle of a Technology: Why It Is So Difficult for Large Companies to Innovate, Don Norman, Nielsen-Norman Group, 1998-10-16; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Don Norman, Nielsen-Norman Group, "The life cycle of a technology: Why it is so difficult for large companies to innovate" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1998-10-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - A Human-Centered Architecture for an Interactive Workspace, Terry Winograd, Stanford Computer Science, 1998-10-2; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Terry Winograd, Stanford Computer Science, "A Human-Centered Architecture for an Interactive Workspace" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1998-10-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Interacting with Informatino: Lessons from Stanford Digital Library Project, Andreas Paepcke, Stanford Digital Library Project, 1998-10-23; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Andreas Paepcke, Stanford Digital Library Project, "Interacting with Information: Lessons from Stanford Digital library Project" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1998-10-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Sensors: The Next Wave in Information Technology, Paul Saffo, Institute for the Future, 1998-10-30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Paul Saffo, Institute for the Future, "Sensors: The Next wave in information technology" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1998-10-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - CommandTalk: A Spoken-Language Interface to a Battlefield Simulator, John Dowding, SRI International and NASA Ames Research, 1998-10-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - John Dowding & Robert Moore, SRI International and NASA Ames Research, "CommandTalk: A Spoken-Language Interface to a Battlefield Simulator" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1998-10-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - StarCursors in ContentSpace: Abstractions of People and Places, Paul Rankin, Philips Research, Redhill UK, 1998-11-13; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Paul Rankin, Philips Research, Redhill, UK, "StarCursors in ContentSpace: Abstractions of people and places" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1998-11-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Dynamic Abstraction, Scott Snibbe, Interval Research, 1998-11-20; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Scott Snibbe, Interval Research, "Dynamic Abstraction" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1998-11-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Toward Affective Interface, Rosalind Picard, MIT Media Lab, 1998-11-6; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Rosalind Picard, MIT Media Lab, "Toward Affective Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1998-11-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - WBI: Intermediaries for Manipulating Web Content, Rob Barrett, IBM Almaden Research, 1998-1-16; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Rob Barrett, IBM Almaden Research, "WBI: Intermediaries for Manipulating Web Content" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1998-1-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Kinesthetic Thinking: Interaction Design without Programming, Dag Svanaes, Norwegian University of Science and Tech, 1998-1-23; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Dag Svanaes, Norwegian University of Science and Technology, "Kinesthetic Thinking: Interaction Design without Programming" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1998-1-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Access to Tacit Embodied Knowledge: Force Sensation and Conceptualization, Miriam Reiner, Techninon, Israel, 1998-12-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Miriam Reiner, Techninon, Isreal, "Access to tacit embodied knowledge: Force sensation and conceptualization" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1998-12-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Apple University Design Project 1992-1997: A Retrospective, Harry Saddler, Xerox PARC, 1998-1-30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Harry Saddler, Xerox PARC, "The Apple University Design Project 1992-1997: A Retrospective" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1998-1-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Intergrating User Interface Agents with Conventional Applications, Henry Lieberman, MIT Media Lab, 1998-1-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Henry Lieberman, MIT Media Lab, "Integrating User Interface Agents with Conventional Applications" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1998-1-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Inmates are Running the Asylum, Alan Cooper, Cooper Interactive Design, 1998-2-13; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Alan Cooper, Cooper Interaction Design, "The Inmates are Running the Asylum" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1998-2-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Alan Cooper (CS547 Winograd), 1998-2-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Eyes Have It: User Interfaces for Infromation Visualization, Ben Shneiderman, University of Maryland, 1998-2-20; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ben Shneiderman, University of Maryland, "The Eyes Have It: User Interfaces for Information Visualization" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1998-2-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - AHA: Audio HTML Access, Frankie James, Stanford, 1998-2-27; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Frankie James, Stanford, "AHA: Audio HTML Access" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1998-2-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Probability, Utility and Human-Computer Interaction, Eric Horvitz, Microsoft Research, 1998-2-6; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Eric Horvitz, Microsoft Research, "Probability, Utility and Human-Computer Interaction" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1998-2-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - 3DDI: 3D Direct Interaction, John Canny, UC Berkeley, 1998-3-13; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - John Canny, UC Berkeley, "3DDI: 3D Direct Interaction" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1998-3-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - New Technologies for Learning, Charles Kerns, Stanford Learning Lab, 1998-3-6; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Charles Kern, George Toye, Stanford Learning Lab, "New Technologies for Learning" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1998-3--6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Graphical Style Sheets: Reusable Representations of Domain-Specific Information Graphics, Ramon Felciano, Stanford Section on Medical Informatics, 1998-4-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ramon Felciano, Stanford Section on Medical Infomatics, "Graphical Style Sheets: Reusable Representations of Domain-Specific Information Graphics" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1998-4-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Design of the Palm Pilot, Rob Haitani, 3Com (Palm Computing), 1998-4-17; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Rob Haitani, 3Com (Palm Computing), "The Design of the Palm Pilot" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1998-4-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Distance Matters: Intellectual Work Among Geographically Separated Group Members, Gary Olson, University of Michigan, 1998-4-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Gary & Judith Olson, University of Michigan, "Distance Matters: Intellectual Work Among Geographically Separated Group Members" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1998-4-24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Comic Chat: Research and Productization War Stories, David Kurlander, Microsoft Research, 1998-4-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - David Kurlander, Microsoft Research, "Comic Chat: Research and Productization War Stories" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1998-4-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - The Architecture of Identity, Phil Agre, UC San Diego, 1998-5-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Phil Agre, UC San Diego, "The Architecture of Identity" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1998-5-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Experience from the Design of Visio, Peter Mullen, Visio, 1998-5-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Peter Mullen, Visio, "Experience from the Design of Visio" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1998-5-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Communicating with Machines Using Speech, Gesture, and Facial Expression, Justine Cassell, MIT Media Lab, 1998-5-22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Justine Cassell, MIT Media Lab, "Communicating with Machines Using Speech, Gesture, and Facial Expression" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1998-5-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Work Beyond the Desktop: Our Cooperative Building and Roomware Projects, Erich J. Neohold, GMD-IPSI & T. U. Darmstadt, 1998-5-29; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Erich J. Neuhold, GMD-IPSI & T.U. Darmstadt, "Work beyond the Desktop: Our Cooperative Building and Roomware Projects" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1998-5-29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Persuasive Computers: Examples, Perspectives and Research Directions, BJ Fogg, SUN Microsystems, Stanford, 1998-5-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - BJ Fogg, Sun Microsystems, Stanford, "Persuasive Computers: Examples, perspectives and research directions" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1998-5-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Computer-Related Design at the Royal College of Art, Gillian Crampton Smith, Royal College of Art, 1998-9-25; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Gillian Crampton Smith, Royal College Of Art, London, "Computer-Related Design at the Royal College of Art" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1998-9-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Scenarios of Future User-Interface Design, Aaron Marcus, Aaron Marcus and Associates, 1999-10-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Aaron Marcus, Aaron Marcus and Associates, "Scenarios of Future User-Interface Design" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1999-10-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Computer-Aided Design of User Interfaces, Angel Puerta, Red Whale Software, 1999-10-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Angel Puerta, Red Whale Software, "Computer-Aided Design of User Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1999-10-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - The Soft Machine - Design in the Cyborg Age, Marie O'Mahony, Dircon, 1999-10-22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Marie O'Mahony, "The Soft Machine - Design in the Cyborg Age" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1999-10-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Cliff Nass, Stanford Communications Dept. and CSLI, "How Human is Human-Computer Interaction?" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1999-10-29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Visual Language: Global Communication for the 21st Century, Bob Horn, Stanford CSLI and Info Mapping, 1999-10-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Bob Horn, Stanford CSLI and Information Mapping, "Visual Language: Global Communication for the 21st Century" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1999-10-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - From Handmade Books to HTML and Beyond, Abbe Don, Abbe Don Interactive, 1999-11-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Abbe Don, Abbe Don Interactive, "From Handmade Books to HTML and Beyond" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1999-11-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Perspective Taking Amongst Distributed Workers, Pamela Hinds, Stanford Dept. of Industrial Engineering and Engineering Management, 1999-11-19; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Pamela Hinds, Stanford Dept. of Industrial Engineering and Engineering Management, "Perspective Taking Amongst Distributed Workers" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1999-11-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Recent Research at the NYU Media Research Lab, Ken Perlin, NYU Media Research Lab, 1999-11-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ken Perlin, NYU Media Research Lab, "Recent Research at the NYU Media Research Lab" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1999-11-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Putting Work Document Collections Online, Lucy Suchman, Xerox PARC, 1999-1-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Lucy Suchman, Xerox PARC, "Putting Work Document Collections Online" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1999-1-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - As If Users Mattered: Research in Human Centered Design, Patrick Whitney, Technology, 1999-1-22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Patrick Whitney & Kei Sato, Institute of Design, Illinois Institute of Technology, "As If Users Mattered: Research in Human Centered Design" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1999-1-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Internet-based Interactive Character Design: From Agents to Avatars, Steve DiPaola, communities.com, 1999-12-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Steve Dipaola, communities.com, "Internet-based Interactive Character Design: From Agents to Avatars" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1999-12-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Interfacing Telerobotics to the Net: Experiments in Telepistemology, Ken Goldberg, UC Berkeley, 1999-1-29; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ken Goldberg, UC Berkeley, "Interfacing Telerobotics to the Net: Experiments in Telepistemology" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1999-1-29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Speech Recognition: From Labratory to Consumer - Half a Million Callers a Day Can't Be Wrong!, Hy Murveit, Nuance Communications, 1999-1-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Hy Murveit, Nuance Communications, "Speech Recognition: From Laboratory to Consumer - Half a Million Callers a Day can't be Wrong!" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1999-1-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Informal User Interfaces for Shared Note Taking, James Landay, UC Berkeley, 1999-2-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - James Landay, UC Berkeley, "Informal User Interfaces for Shared Note Taking" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1999-2-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Consumer Multimedia Organization and Retrieval, Allan Kuchinsky, Hewlett Packard Lab, 1999-2-19; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Allan Kuchinsky, Hewlett Packard Laboratories, "Consumer Multimedia Organization and Retrieval" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1999-2-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)